indiamp3.com 2017-12-14

# IndiaMp3.Com - Privacy Policy

**INDIAMP3.COM - PRIVACY POLICY**

Privacy is becoming a major concern on the Internet now, because of the popularity of the Internet some businesses have taken advantage of the huge amounts of data they have collected through their web sites by 'spamming' or by adding you to annoying mailing lists which you don't even remember signing up to. Indiamp3.com does NOT require you to disclose personal information anywhere on the site, so it's not a major problem. However in the event that we do adopt features to the site which require you to fill out forms requiring your personal information we will make it OPTIONAL and we will NEVER, EVER make the information accessible to the public, sell it to anyone or use it for any purposes except for our own research. In addition when using our website your IP address is not stored or logged in any way!

**Cookies & 3rd Party Advertisements:**

Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on your site. Google's use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to your users based on their visit to your sites and other sites on the Internet. Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the [Google ad and content network privacy policy](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html).

We allow third-party companies to serve ads and/or collect certain anonymous information when you visit our web site. These companies may use non-personally identifiable information (e.g., click stream information, browser type, time and date, subject of advertisements clicked or scrolled over) during your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements about goods and services likely to be of greater interest to you. These companies typically use a cookie or third party web beacon to collect this information. To learn more about this behavioral advertising practice or to opt-out of this type of advertising, you can visit <http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp>.
